(Howard:)Okay, so I wasn't
exactly John Glenn up there,
(Howard:)but I've changed,
I'm a different man now.
(Howard:)I'm a little insulted that you guys
don't think I can handle it.
(Mike M:)You know you're gonna have to go
through survival training again.
(Penny:)Really?
You've got to get me out of this!
(Doctor:)What do you want me to do?
You're perfectly healthy.
Check my blood pressure again!
(Howard:)I can get it higher,
just give me a second.
(Mrs Wolowitz(on phone):)Hello?
-Hi, Ma. How are you?
How I am is not dead!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)But you wouldn't know that,
because you don't love me enough
to pick up the phone!
Go, go, go!
For all you know, l could have
slipped in the tub and drowned!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)That's what happened
to your Aunt Ida!
(Raj:)Wow.
(Raj:)Howard, I'm so sorry your blood
pressure was off the charts.
Me, too. The doctor was willing
to fudge the results,
(Howard:)but it just seemed
so darned dishonest.